<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bitcoin Lightning on Felipe Brunet</title>
    <link>/en/tags/bitcoin-lightning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bitcoin Lightning on Felipe Brunet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/tags/bitcoin-lightning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Ecommerce Site</title>
      <link>/en/projects/ecom-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/ecom-site/</guid>
      <description>bitpointburger.cl
Great smashed burgers in Pichilemu, Chile.
Site made with Wordpress, Woocommerce and very few plugins, to maximize speed and responsiveness. Includes traditional payment gateways and also Bitcoin Lightning payments with the LN Pagos Latam plugin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icripto POS Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/en/posts/icripto-pos-priv-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/icripto-pos-priv-policy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We do not use nor collect your Personal Data.
Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LN Pagos Latam</title>
      <link>/en/projects/ln-pagos-latam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/ln-pagos-latam/</guid>
      <description>A Wordpress plugin to enable Bitcoin Lightning payments straight to the merchant&amp;rsquo;s account in Buda. The is a merchant can offer bitcoin payments and still be able to easily receive local currency, by selling and transfer the money from the exchange to the merchant&amp;rsquo;s bank account. The Github repository URL is the following:
https://github.com/felipebrunet/lnpagos-latam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icripto POS</title>
      <link>/en/projects/icripto-pos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/icripto-pos/</guid>
      <description>Esta es una app que permite cobrar bitcoin usando distintos servicios de cobro de bitcoin, tales como LNBits, BTCPay o incluso una Lightning Address (WIP).
Links asociados:
URL Play Store Repositorio Github Adicionalmente permite cobrar bitcoin dirigidos directamente a servicios de los exchanges Buda (Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Perú) y Bitaroo (Australia).
De este modo es simple cobrar bitcoin en forma presencial, siendo esta app ideal para que incluso los dependientes y empleados puedan usar esta aplicacion desde sus celulares o tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
